
question_data = [
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "King Gizzard &amp; The Lizard Wizard&#039;s album &quot;Nonagon Infinity&quot; can be looped seamlessly.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "In architecture, a &quot;pecklesteiner&quot; is a set of doors that overlap each other when closed, and can be locked through a single keyhole.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "Nutella is produced by the German company Ferrero.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "Did Michael Jackson invent the moonwalk?",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "A scientific study on peanuts in bars found traces of over 100 unique specimens of urine.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "It is automatically considered entrapment in the United States if the police sell you illegal substances without revealing themselves.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "The Sun rises from the North.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "The Great Wall of China is visible from the moon.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "March 10th is also known as Mar10 Day.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "You can legally drink alcohol while driving in Mississippi.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    }
  ]